buytome.com 2019-03-21

# Privacy Policy - Help Center - BuyToMe.com - Buy China shop at Wholesale Price By Online English Taobao Agent

  * Help Center
  * New User

### Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy

BuyToMe respect your privacy. This Privacy Statement informs you how we collect and handle your personal information which you provide to us as you access and interact with this Website.

Information collected

The information about you which we may collect through this Web Site varies depending on how you use this Web Site. We will collect information through any electronic forms you submit via this Web Site, or other messages you send us by e-mail.

In common with many web sites, we may collect information such as the date and time of your visit to this Web Site, the pages accessed and any information downloaded. This information does not identify you as an individual and is used for statistical, reporting and Web Site administration and maintenance purposes only.

How we use your information

The information BuyToMe collects to understand your needs and interests to help BuyToMe provide a better service. For example, BuyToMe may use your information to

●  complete a transaction or order;  
●  allow you to participate in surveys and promotions;  
●  prevent and detect fraud or other malicious activity;  
●  improve or update our services;  
●  help you solve some problems concerning our service or website;

 How we share your information

BuyToMe may provide personal information to

●  our service providers who assist us in providing this Web Site and our services (for example internet and technology service providers, mail houses, delivery companies);  
●  organizations with whom we have co-promotional arrangements (and any agents used in administering such arrangements);

BuyToMe does not provide your personal information to third party organizations for their marketing purposes. We will not sell, rent or lease your personal information to others except as described in this Statement.

 Links to other web sites

 This Web Site may contain links to third party web sites. Any such linked web sites may contain their own privacy policies or statements and those third parties, and not BuyToMe, are responsible for informing you about their security and privacy practices.

 Security

BuyToMe value your personal information and take great effort to protect the security of your personal information. However, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed as completely secure. BuyToMe cannot ensure or warrant the 100% security of your information. We will try our best to protect your information, but you are at your own risk.

 Changes to this statement

BuyToMe will post any changes to this Privacy Statement on this Web Site, please check our Privacy Statement from time to time.

Contact details

If you have any comments or questions about our Privacy Statement, please send E-mail to:Service@BuyToMe.com
